Guide to the Re-Imagining Collection, 1993-2016 RL.11352
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Re-Imagining Conferences, 1993-2000
  - 1995 Gathering - Soundings: Re-Imagining the Word, 1995-11-03/1995-11-04; 6
    - Listening to Sophiaword, 1995-11-03/1995-11-04; 33
      - 1995_Unbinding_the_Word_Miriam_Therese_Winter_Part_B.mp3, 0:47:40 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - Audiocassette 1 (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0027)
      - Audiocassette 2 (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0028)
    - Giving Voice to Sophiaword, 1995-11-03/1995-11-04; 34
      - 1995_Giving_Voice_to_Sophiaword_Carmen_Valenzuela.mp3, 0:08:27 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 1995_Giving_Voice_to_Sophiaword_Joy_Mincey_Powell.mp3, 0:06:06 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 1995_Giving_Voice_to_Sophiaword_Maren_Hinderlie.mp3, 0:13:09 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 1995_Giving_Voice_to_Sophiaword_Pamela_Carter_Joern.mp3, 0:08:24 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 1995_Giving_Voice_to_Sophiaword_Sister_Holy_Spirit_DeSouza.mp3, 0:08:45 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 1995_Ritual_6.mp3, 0:25:46 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - Audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0029)
    - Rebirthed by Sophiaword, 1995-11-03/1995-11-04; 35
      - 1995_Comments_from_Attendees.mp3, 0:26:10 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 1995_Ritual_7.mp3, 0:22:57 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 1995_Volunteer_Recognition.mp3, 0:06:27 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - Audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0030)
  - 1996 Gathering: Naming, Claiming, and Re-Imagining Power, 1996-11-01/1996-11-02; 7
    - ReImagining Power as Embodied Spirituality, 1996-11-01/1996-11-02; 36
      - 1996_Ritual_1.mp3, 0:17:01 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
        Gathering
      - 1996_Holy_Play_1.mp3, 0:30:54 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
        Holy Play
      - 1996_Holy_Play_2.mp3, 0:27:28 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - Audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0031)
        Friday Evening Gathering Ritual and Holy Play. Conversation with Letty, Chris and Joan.
      - 1996_Russell-Timmerman-Smith_part_1.mp3, 0:22:02 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
        Round Table Discussion
      - 1996_Russell-Timmerman-Smith_part_2.mp3, 0:35:37 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 1996_Ritual_2.mp3, 0:17:36 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
        Ritual of Milk and Honey
      - Audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0032)
        Friday Evening Conversation w/Letty, Chris and Joan / Ritual of Milk and Honey
    - ReImagining Power through Welcomed Difference, 1996-11-01/1996-11-02; 37
      - 1996_Ritual_3.mp3, 0:12:40 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
        Saturday Morning Gathering
      - 1996_Holy_Play_3.mp3, 0:32:34 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - Audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0033)
        Saturday Morn: Community Ritual, Holy Play Conversation w/Letty, Rene and Vivian
      - 1996_Unpacking_Your_Knapsack.mp3, 0:15:19 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
        Unpacking Your Knapsack
      - Russell-Whiterabbit-Nelsen_Part_1.mp3, 0:34:27 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
        Unpacking Your Knapsack Roundtable Discussion
      - Russell-Whiterabbit-Nelsen_Part_2.mp3, 0:15:58 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 1996_Talking_Circle_on_Racism.mp3, 0:04:25 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
        Unpacking Your Knapsack Talking Circle
      - 4_1996_Meal_Blessing_Ritual_4.mp3, 0:09:10 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
    - ReImagining Community Meeting, 1996-11-01/1996-11-02; 38
      - 1_1996_Re-Imagining_Community_Meeting_(Jo_Ringgenberg_and_Marylee_Fithian).mp3, 0:18:00 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 2_1996_Ritual_5_Sophia's_Song_and_Readings.mp3, 0:05:50 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - Audiocassette (Box AV1, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0034)
        Saturday Morning: Conversation w/Letty, Rene and Vivian. Transition Ritual. Comm Meeting.
    - Reimagining Power Through Ecclesial Subversion, 1996-11-01/1996-11-02; 39
      - 1_1996_Ritual_6_Soon_Enough_(Genesis_Exodus_and_Luke).mp3, 0:25:42 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 1996_Eily_Marlowe.mp3, 0:11:41 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
        Story Telling
      - 1996_Heather_Murray_Elkins.mp3, 0:21:26 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 1996_Katie_Johnson.mp3, 0:23:42 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - 1996_Marchelle_Hallman.mp3, 0:09:41 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - Audiocassette (Box AV2, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0035)
        Saturday Afternoon Apple Ritual, Stories by Eily, Marchelle, Katie and Heather
      - 3_1996_Talking_Circle.mp3, 0:06:50 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
        Talking Circle Stories of Institutional Subversion
      - 1996_Elkins_-_Russell_.mp3, 0:27:29 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
        Roundtable Discussion
      - 1996_Q_&_A_with_Presenters.mp3, 0:19:09 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
        Talkback Circle Q&A
      - 2_1996_Closing_the_Gathering_Ritual_7.mp3, 0:01:38 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
        Closing the Gathering
      - 1_1996_Closing_Announcements.mp3, 0:22:33 (Digital-materials RL11352-SET-0001, E-folder RL11352-LFF-0001)
      - Audiocassette (Box AV2, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0036)
        Saturday Afternoon: Conversation by Letty and Heather. Talking Circle Q and A. Closing.
  - 1998 Re-Imagining Revival, 1998-04-16/1998-04-19; 8
    - 1. Voices Gather, Lighting the Lamps and The Table Blessing, 1998-04-16/1998-04-19; 40
      - Audiocassette (Box AV2, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0053)
    - 2. Welcome and Blessing, Mary Bednarowski and Rita Nakashima Brock, 1998-04-16/1998-04-19; 41
      - Audiocassette (Box AV2, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0054)
    - 3. Rita Nakashima Brock - Continued Trimming Our Lamps, 1998-04-16/1998-04-19; 42
      - Audiocassette (Box AV2, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0055)
    - 4. Gathering Our Voice, Blessing Litany, Brigalia Bam, 1998-04-16/1998-04-19; 43
      - Audiocassette (Box AV2, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0056)
    - 5. Beverly Harrison - Presentation Invitation, 1998-04-16/1998-04-19; 44
      - Audiocassette (Box AV2, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0057)
    - 6. Mary Ann Lundy - Presentation, 1998-04-16/1998-04-19; 45
      - Audiocassette (Box AV2, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0058)
    - 7. Delores Williams - Presentation, 1998-04-16/1998-04-19; 46
      - Audiocassette (Box AV2, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0059)
    - 8. Gathering Our Spices, Cooking Up Our Way, Amme Patrick - Presentation, 1998-04-16/1998-04-19; 47
      - Audiocassette (Box AV2, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0060)
    - 9. Carter Heyward - Presentation, 1998-04-16/1998-04-19; 48
      - Audiocassette (Box AV2, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0061)
    - 10. Mari Castellanos - Presentation, 1998-04-16/1998-04-19; 49
      - Audiocassette (Box AV2, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0062)
    - 11. Blessing, One Voice One Body, Church Supper, More Music from '98, 1998-04-16/1998-04-19; 50
      - Audiocassette (Box AV2, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0063)
    - 12. Musimbi Kanyoro - Presentation, 1998-04-16/1998-04-19; 51
      - Audiocassette (Box AV2, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0064)
    - 13. Barbara Lundblad - Revival Worship, 1998-04-16/1998-04-19; 52
      - Audiocassette (Box AV2, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0065)
    - 14. Music from Re-Imagining '98, 1998-04-16/1998-04-19; 53
      - Audiocassette (Box AV2, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0066)
    - 15. Barbara Lundblad - Revival Worship Continued, 1998-04-16/1998-04-19; 54
      - Audiocassette (Box AV2, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0067)
  - Millenial Gathering of the Re-Imagining Community, 2000-10-26/2000-10-28; 9
    - 1. Welcome/Opening Celebration, Kathy Black - part 1, 2000-10-26/2000-10-28; 55
      - Audiocassette (Box AV2, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0068)
    - 2. Opening Celebration, Kathy Black - part 2, 2000-10-26/2000-10-28; 56
      - Audiocassette (Box AV2, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0069)
    - 3. Gathering Music/Rebecca Walker Response/Table Time/Speak Outs tape 1, 2000-10-26/2000-10-28; 57
      - Audiocassette (Box AV2, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0070)
    - 4. Gathering Music/Rebecca Walker Response/Table Time/Speak Outs tape 2, 2000-10-26/2000-10-28; 58
      - Audiocassette (Box AV2, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0071)
    - 5. Gathering Music/Mary Daly Response/Table Time/Speak Outs - tape 1, 2000-10-26/2000-10-28; 59
      - Audiocassette (Box AV2, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0072)
    - 6. Gathering Music/Mary Daly Response/Table Time/Speak Outs - tape 2, 2000-10-26/2000-10-28; 60
      - Audiocassette (Box AV2, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0073)
    - 7. Kelly Connole and Evening Prayer, Music by Bread for the Journey, 2000-10-26/2000-10-28; 61
      - Audiocassette (Box AV2, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0074)
    - 8. Gathering Music/Thandeka Response/Table Time/Speak Outs - Tape 1, 2000-10-26/2000-10-28; 62
      - Audiocassette (Box AV2, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0075)
    - 9. Gathering Music/Thandeka Response/Table Time/Speak Outs - Tape 2, 2000-10-26/2000-10-28; 63
      - Audiocassette (Box AV2, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0076)
    - 10. Community Presentations, Chris Smith/Amy Blumenshine - tape 1, 2000-10-26/2000-10-28; 64
      - Audiocassette (Box AV2, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0077)
    - 11. Community Presentations, Chris Smith/Amy Blumenshine - tape 2, 2000-10-26/2000-10-28; 65
      - Audiocassette (Box AV2, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0078)
    - 12. Closing Celebration, Delores Williams/Music, 2000-10-26/2000-10-28; 66
      - Audiocassette (Box AV2, Audio-cassette RL11352-CS-0079)
- Papers, 1993-2014
  - Re-Imagining Conference-Minneapolis, November 4-7, 1993 (Box 1)
  - Re-Imagining post-conference reflections, 1993 (Box 1)
  - Press clippings following conference, 1993-1994 (Box 1)
  - 'To Sing Fiercely, Tenderly, Knowingly': A Study of the 1993 Re-Imagining Conference, 1994 (Box 1)
  - Re-Imagining Revival Event- St. Paul, April 16-19, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Press clippings following the conference, 1998-1999 (Box 1)
  - Learnings from the Planning of Re-Imagining Revival, November 3, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Re-Imagining Revisited Event- Minnetonka, April 17-19, 2009 (Box 1)
  - Re-Imagining Millennial Conference- Minneapolis, October 26-28, 2000 (Box 1)
  - Materials sent to Burke Library (Union Theological Seminary), 1999-2003 (Box 1)
  - Papers from dissolution process, 2003 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence about the Collection, 2014 (Box 1)
  - Bless Sophia, 2003 (Box 1)